🎵 Guys, my flight is in less than 12 hours.
I'm solo traveling to China, specifically Hong Kong, for the first time ever.
so nervous but i'm also super excited i've done so much research i've planned an
itinerary pack my bags and practice my cantonese so without further ado let's go to
china
Hello guys from
Hong Kong.
I have finally made it.
That flight was so long and I only really slept four to five hours at
the hotel here.
I am so jet lagged.
It's 7 15 right now and I'm actually gonna head out to get some dim
sum because I want to start off the trip right and I have the most
jam-packed itinerary.
So without further ado, let's get going.
This is the view from my hotel room.
You can see the mountain in the back there and condo buildings on there.
I think that's so
cool.
Okay,
I finally found it.
It's on the corner right here.
I'm so embarrassed right now.
I cannot.
It's okay, I think I'm the only foreigner in this place right now.
That's okay.
We learn.
Yeah, we learn.
I just got some green tea.
I honestly didn't understand the options, but I'll drink anything.
I'm easy going.
I'm not here to impose on anybody.
That's super, super good.
I'm going to try this one right now.
I was literally joking with Ainsley and Garbo that there might be a little bit
of a language barrier and I might not receive what I order.
The woman did speak English, but then she just gave me something else, so that's
okay.
I think it's pork and green onion.
It's not bad, but it's not what I ordered.
It's not good.
I don't know.
Okay, I'm walking underneath something, but it is raining, so I just picked up this
umbrella from a convenience store.
I'm headed to this really popular coffee shop that does really cool latte art, and
so I wanted to have a little caffeine before I went to hike Victoria Peak,
but I'm not sure if I should go anymore because of the rain, so...
So
I decided to hike Victoria Peak anyways.
It is raining so much.
I haven't experienced rain like this in such a long time.
Probably last time I went to Vietnam.
My pants are soaking, but it's honestly really quiet.
So I'm having a great time.
incline everywhere.
But I'm having fun!
All of my stuff, including me, is soaking wet, but I finally made it to
the viewpoint that I was hiking towards because it has this really great view of
Victoria Harbor.
So glad that I waited out the rain because look at this view.
Made it to the peak and I think I'm gonna get a lemon iced tea
because I deserve a treat.
My iced lemon tea has been born and
they gave me me vanilla syrup.
It's good.
I just need like five of these.
I am back at my hotel and I just picked up a ham and egg
bun because I want to go to a really well-known bakery for my first pineapple
bun and egg tart in Hong Kong.
I just came back to change my clothes because I was soaked to the bone
hiking and I'm so cold.
Can you tell that I've never opened a bottle before?
I haven't had any water today and I seriously regret not getting something before my
hike but time for my ham and egg bun.
This thing is huge.
So good.
I
feel
like an old lady.
I'm getting ready for bed and it's only 8 30 but I have been awake
since 3 30 a.m but of course i have to do my skincare first this
is the mediquipe pdrn pink peptide serum it helps brighten hydrate and strengthen your skin
the salmon dna helps promote skin cell repair and the five peptide complex can improve
skin elasticity and firmness give you that plump and juicy glass skin i usually do
two and a half drops of this roughly spread that all over before going in
with the new affordable glow booster this is the booster pro mini and i swear
by this machine's tech because it maximizes the effects of your skincare it helps your
skin absorb the ingredients better it always leaves my skin feeling way more hydrated and
you can use it up to five to ten minutes three times a day you
go up to level two or level three i usually keep it on level three
My skin loves when I use these two together
I just love the redesign of this because it's more compact it can fit in
my tiny travel skincare bag And it's more affordable so more of you guys can
get it There's going to be a spring sale on march 25th Make sure to
check out the link in my description box below and lastly i'm going to lock
in all my skincare with the medikube Gel mask it's the prn pink collagen gel
mask If you guys have seen my other videos and you've definitely seen me wear
this multiple times I feel like it really locks in my skincare and is the
perfect ending to my nighttime skincare routine
And now i'm ready to get into bed and elevate my feet because I walked
20 000 steps which is Very abnormal for me and good night guys.
I'll see you in the morning
Hi guys, welcome to day two of hong kong i've just gotten dressed I have
red shoes on and i'm gonna pack my purse And I know this is a
lot of black so i'm breaking it up with this jean jacket It's also a
little bit cold and this is my bag to match my shoes What's in here?
We can do a what's in my bag We have a portable charger two cameras
my gopro and my g7x I have my little airpods, lactate lip balm, and an
extra battery for my DSLR.
Um, oh, I literally just went to go look to show you my DSLR, but
you are my DSLR.
And then my phone and some Hong Kong dollars.
And I have my debit card in here to like withdraw more cash.
And if you're wondering how I'm taking pictures by myself, I'm using this little tripod
that collapses fully and it just fits in this purse.
Like look, it just fits in there.
So without further ado, let's get going.
So lost in the subway station because there's so many floors and there's so many
escalators, but I finally made it and we're going to Australia Dairy Co.
because everyone loves it for Hong Kong style breakfast.
The
Thank you
for
watching.
Music So I'm in Mombok right now and I'm meant to just do a bunch
of shopping and browsing but it's really really busy so I'm feeling a little overwhelmed
and honestly I'm happy to just stand and watch so I've been doing a bit
of that as well
Okay,
I got my first egg tart of my trip.
I got it from this really popular spot.
It was recommended in a few YouTube videos that I've watched and on Redbook, so
let's give it a try.
And it was 7 Hong Kong dollars.
Let's see what it looks like.
That is so good.
looks like.
This crust is super crisp but it's still flaky and buttery if that makes sense.
I feel like egg tarts in Canada are leaning heavy on the buttery side but
they don't have that like crisp crunch.
There's like so many layers.
Okay, now I am in Cham Shui Po.
It's known to have flea markets on two separate streets and there's this one stand
that I'm looking forward to that has a bunch of vintage cameras so I'm really
excited to check them out.
Ouch.
I almost ate it.
It looks like I came at a really busy time because I think everyone's doing
their groceries right now everything looks so good
i'm not sure if this is the exact one that i'm looking for but i
did find this has a ton of cds and vintage cameras
Guys, I have walked up and down so many of these streets and I'm so
lost and I think I finally found the vintage camera shop that I was looking
for.
I didn't end up getting anything from the second vintage camera store because they didn't
have my dream dream camera and I didn't want to settle and also pay the
same price that I could get on eBay.
So now I'm having three fish balls from the stand that I just found on
the corner.
Okay, one of our last stops of the night is going to be Elegant Tang
Dynasty and I actually found this place from Redbook because all the girlies on there
were posting these really cute magnets of the subway station.
I hope to get a bunch.
I just finished therapy, it is now 2 30 in the morning and I thought
I would show you guys my haul so far.
I've actually been really proud of my self-control and I haven't just been buying every
single thing that I've seen.
I got all of these from Elegant Tang Dynasty.
These are mahjong tile keychains that I thought were really cute.
This is like the subway station sign.
I got this one and then this one is the classic Hong Kong milk tea.
I also did end up getting one digital camera.
It's the Olympus U model.
It's fully functioning and so this is the shop if you want to go and
support this woman.
She was super sweet and super patient with me.
I was testing a bunch of cameras out.
Now I'm gonna head to bed because I have a full day ahead.
Good morning guys, it is day three in Hong Kong and I am leaving the
house very very late today This is a little sneak peek of my outfit
You guys you have no idea how happy I am right now because the sun
is out finally I'm in Happy Valley for the morning because I'm going to this
really popular spot for Hong Kong style breakfast so
so
Okay, I'm walking through Happy Valley now.
Breakfast was actually insanely good.
I am just so happy that I went there.
And when I was on the tram, we passed by this huge green space and
there's a bunch of people playing sports.
I thought it was part of Hong Kong U, but I looked it up and
it looks like just a regular public park, but it is literally so well maintained.
I thought it had to be a part of the university because I was like,
there's no way this is like a city park.
think it is just like a recreational space which is so cool because there's not
a lot of those in Toronto if any.
Okay I left Happy Valley and guys this weather is making me so happy but
I definitely took the weekdays for granted because it is so busy.
I don't know if it's just the area I'm in.
I'm on Lee Tong Avenue and I'm just doing a little bit of shopping and
browsing.
I'm headed to Stussy right now.
I want to get one of those April shirts that have Hong Kong on the
back because I don't I don't want a classic I heart Hong Kong shirt, but
I do want some sort of souvenir and I love a good back print on
a shirt.
This is the longest queue I've seen in Hong Kong.
I'm back in central and this time I'm at Bakehouse, this was the most recommended
spot for bake tarts.
And then I also am going to walk over to Vision Bakery and see if
they have this matcha tart that one of you guys DMed me that you love,
but they're only sold after noon and it's already like 4.30pm so I'm not sure
if they're already sold out, but we're going to check.
I got two things from
Bakehouse and I got a quinamon from Vision.
This I am so excited about.
This is what the egg tart looks like.
This is definitely the most baked out of all the egg tarts I've had.
Oh my god.
I thought just so many people were recommending it.
It was going to be like overhyped and I know it's like a tourist spot
and that's why there's a queue every single time.
but no this is worth all of the hype now i'm upset that i only
got one
i also got this dessert from bakehouse
i don't know if i love that the middle part where there's like custard and
strawberry is really good but the outside part of it is kind of dry now
we're going to get into what i got from vision this is my quinamon
it's really good
but just tastes like it was baked 12 hours ago i should have come earlier
this is better than the strawberry danish but it's not better than the egg tart
and i wouldn't order it again okay and that marks the end of my street
treat review but anyways i'm headed to kennedy town now to hopefully catch the sunset
by the water and also have dinner there because I can't just keep eating treats.
So there's this really pretty photo up in Kennedy Town.
And it's in a basketball court.
And the shot is taken through the gate of the basketball court.
And so I'm going to have to disturb some of these people.
You can see there's a bunch of people.
Okay, but it looks like they roped it off because they knew how busy it's
been